http://www.innovationsfcu.org/privacy-policy/

Amazon Phone Scam
- Beware of new phone scam trying to get your personal information ... Learn More
Coronavirus Scam Alert
- Beware of new phishing attacks and bogus emails requesting money or your personal information ... Learn More
Branch Updates:
Read the latest information on our branch operations related to the pandemic...learn more
FACTS
What does Innovations Federal Credit Union do with your personal information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and account balances
Account transactions and checking account information
Credit card or other debt and transaction history
When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Innovations Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Innovations Federal Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes- such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes- to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes- information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes- information about your creditworthiness
No
We don’t share
For our nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don’t share
Questions?
Call 850-233-4400 or go to innovationsfcu.org
What we do
How does Innovations Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Innovations Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or apply for a financing
show your driver’s license or give us your contact information
make a wire transfer
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Innovations Federal Credit Union has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. The can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Innovations Federal Credit Union does not share with our nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include advertising/marketing agencies, CUNA Mutual Group’s MEMBERCONNECT, and loan recapture programs.
Questions?
If you have additional questions, please call 850.233.4400. You may download this Privacy Policy in PDF format.
?
FAQs
Back to top
